Let me think about that ...
How I'd best describe it?
So perhaps think of your existing applications
as this old place.
For a long time people there were happy.
They came up with new ideas.
They were productive.
And everything prospered.
But then things started to change.
People needed new ideas faster.
Applications were built in a traditional way
you'd call them "monolithic".
In simple words they were just big
and complex and a little bit nasty.
Hard to manage and maintain.
Incredibly difficult to get people excited
to work on developing new services
and transforming organizations.
Then they heard of a place where
new ideas flourished and people were excited
to bring them to life.
This is the land of cloud native application development.
They were collaborating with each other a lot more.
They were bringing new innovation and new ideas out.
You didn't feel like, you know, when you were
in these places you were always responding to change,
you were the change.
It's DevOps.
It's containers.
It's microservices.
And it's hybrid cloud.
It's really about changing your mindset
to embrace, you know, what's important with regard
to building application services quicker.
At Red Hat, we help organizations
make strides in all of these areas and go
from spending the majority of their time
focused on maintenance,
to prioritizing building new things
and growing their businesses.
And that is cloud native app development.